Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-123 (1971: July 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-124 (1971: July 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-125 (1971: July 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-126 (1971: July 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-127 (1971: July 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-128 (1971: July 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-129 (1971: July 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-130 (1971: July 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-131 (1971: July 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-132 (1971: July 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-133 (1971: July 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-134 (1971: July 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-135 (1971: July 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-136 (1971: July 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-137 (1971: July 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-138 (1971: July 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-139 (1971: July 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-140 (1971: July 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-141 (1971: July 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-142 (1971: July 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.71-143 (1971: July 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-144 (1971: Aug. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-145 (1971: Aug. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-146 (1971: Aug. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-147 (1971: Aug. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-148 (1971: Aug. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-149 (1971: Aug. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-150 (1971: Aug. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-151 (1971: Aug. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-152 (1971: Aug. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-153 (1971: Aug. 13)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-154 (1971: Aug. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-155 (1971: Aug. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-156 (1971: Aug. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-157 (1971: Aug. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-158 (1971: Aug. 20)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-159 (1971: Aug. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-160 (1971: Aug. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-161 (1971: Aug. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-162 (1971: Aug. 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-163 (1971: Aug. 27)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-164 (1971: Aug. 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.71-165 (1971: Aug. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-166 (1971: Sep. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-167 (1971: Sep. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-168 (1971: Sep. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-169 (1971: Sep. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-168 (1971: Sep. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-169 (1971: Sep. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-170 (1971: Sep. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-173 (1971: Sep. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-174 (1971: Sep. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-175 (1971: Sep. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-176 (1971: Sep. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-177 (1971: Sep. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-178 (1971: Sep. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-179 (1971: Sep. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-180 (1971: Sep. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-181 (1971: Sep. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-182 (1971: Sep. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-183 (1971: Sep. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-184 (1971: Sep. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-185 (1971: Sep. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.71-186 (1971: Sep. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-187 (1971: Oct. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-188 (1971: Oct. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-189 (1971: Oct. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-190 (1971: Oct. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-191 (1971: Oct. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-192 (1971: Oct. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-193 (1971: Oct. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-194 (1971: Oct. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-195 (1971: Oct. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-196 (1971: Oct. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-197 (1971: Oct. 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-198 (1971: Oct. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-199 (1971: Oct. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-200 (1971: Oct. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-201 (1971: Oct. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-202 (1971: Oct. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-203 (1971: Oct. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-204 (1971: Oct. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.71-205 (1971: Oct. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-206 (1971: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-207 (1971: Nov. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-208 (1971: Nov. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-209 (1971: Nov. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-210 (1971: Nov. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-211 (1971: Nov. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-212 (1971: Nov. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-213 (1971: Nov. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-214 (1971: Nov. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-215 (1971: Nov. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-216 (1971: Nov. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-217 (1971: Nov. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-218 (1971: Nov. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-219 (1971: Nov. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-220 (1971: Nov. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-221 (1971: Nov. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-222 (1971: Nov. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-223 (1971: Nov. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-224 (1971: Nov. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.71-225 (1971: Nov. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-226 (1971: Dec. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-227 (1971: Dec. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-228 (1971: Dec. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-229 (1971: Dec. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-230 (1971: Dec. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-231 (1971: Dec. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-232 (1971: Dec. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-233 (1971: Dec. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-234 (1971: Dec. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-235 (1971: Dec. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-236 (1971: Dec. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-237 (1971: Dec. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-238 (1971: Dec. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-239 (1971: Dec. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-240 (1971: Dec. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-241 (1971: Dec. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-242 (1971: Dec. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-243 (1971: Dec. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-244 (1971: Dec. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-245 (1971: Dec. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.71-246 (1971: Dec. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-1 (1972: Jan. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-2 (1972: Jan. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-3 (1972: Jan. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-4 (1972: Jan. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-5 (1972: Jan. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-6 (1972: Jan. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-7 (1972: Jan. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-8 (1972: Jan. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-9 (1972: Jan. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-10 (1972: Jan. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-11 (1972: Jan. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-12 (1972: Jan. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-13 (1972: Jan. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-14 (1972: Jan. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-15 (1972: Jan. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-16 (1972: Jan. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-17 (1972: Jan. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-18 (1972: Jan. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-19 (1972: Jan. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-20 (1972: Jan. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.72-21 (1972: Jan. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-22 (1972: Feb. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-23 (1972: Feb. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-24 (1972: Feb. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-25 (1972: Feb. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-26 (1972: Feb. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-27 (1972: Feb. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-28 (1972: Feb. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-29 (1972: Feb. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-30 (1972: Feb. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-31 (1972: Feb. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-32 (1972: Feb. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-33 (1972: Feb. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-34 (1972: Feb. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-35 (1972: Feb. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-36 (1972: Feb. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-37 (1972: Feb. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-38 (1972: Feb. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-39 (1972: Feb. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-40 (1972: Feb. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.72-41 (1972: Feb. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-42 (1972: Mar. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-43 (1972: Mar. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-44 (1972: Mar. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-45 (1972: Mar. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-46 (1972: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-47 (1972: Mar. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-48 (1972: Mar. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-49 (1972: Mar. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-50 (1972: Mar. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-51 (1972: Mar. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-52 (1972: Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-53 (1972: Mar. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-54 (1972: Mar. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-55 (1972: Mar. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-56 (1972: Mar. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-57 (1972: Mar. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-58 (1972: Mar. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-59 (1972: Mar. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-60 (1972: Mar. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-61 (1972: Mar. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-62 (1972: Mar. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.72-63 (1972: Mar. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-64 (1972: Apr. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-65 (1972: Apr. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-66 (1972: Apr. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-67 (1972: Apr. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-68 (1972: Apr. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-69 (1972: Apr. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-70 (1972: Apr. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-71 (1972: Apr. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-72 (1972: Apr. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-73 (1972: Apr. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-74 (1972: Apr. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-75 (1972: Apr. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-76 (1972: Apr. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-77 (1972: Apr. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-78 (1972: Apr. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-79 (1972: Apr. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-80 (1972: Apr. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-81 (1972: Apr. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-82 (1972: Apr. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.72-83 (1972: Apr. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-84 (1972: May 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-85 (1972: May 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-86 (1972: May 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-87 (1972: May 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-88 (1972: May 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-89 (1972: May 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-90 (1972: May 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-91 (1972: May 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-92 (1972: May 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-93 (1972: May 12)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-94 (1972: May 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-95 (1972: May 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-96 (1972: May 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-97 (1972: May 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-98 (1972: May 19)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-99 (1972: May 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-100 (1972: May 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-101 (1972: May 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-102 (1972: May 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-102 (1972: May 26)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-103 (1972: May 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.72-103 (1972: May 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-104 (1972: June 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-105 (1972: June 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-106 (1972: June 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-107 (1972: June 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-108 (1972: June 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-109 (1972: June 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-110 (1972: June 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-111 (1972: June 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-112 (1972: June 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-113 (1972: June 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-114 (1972: June 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-115 (1972: June 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-116 (1972: June 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-117 (1972: June 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-118 (1972: June 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-119 (1972: June 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-120 (1972: June 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-121 (1972: June 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.72-122 (1972: June 27)